qriyo.in 2017-07-17

# Qriyo - Best Home Tuitions for Academics, Dance, Music, Yoga and 300+ Courses

Personal Information

User hereinafter referred to as (“You”) and Qriyo Infolabs Pvt.Ltd. hereinafter referred to as (“Qriyo”). Qriyo is owner and operator of www.qriyo.com (“the Website”), Qriyo’s Mobile Application for on demand home services [(“Qriyo App”)](https://www.qriyo.com/app/), collectively, including all content provided by Qriyo through the Qriyo App and the Website “Qriyo Service” 

You have right not to supply personally identifiable information. If You intend to view this Qriyo Service and/or or share your data with the Qriyo Service, it is solely at your own volition, risk and after reading and confirming it to this Privacy Policy. 

At the time of using the Qriyo Service you will share certain Personal Information with Qriyo, Qriyo respects your Personal Information. Such Personal Information may include your personal identifiable information such as your name, address, mobile number, your e-mail ids, your age, IP address, payment details and any other personal information which You may share in connection with the services. 

When you use Qriyo’s Service through Qriyo App, Qriyo may use Your mobile device’s ID (the unique identification assigned to a mobile device by the manufacturer). Qriyo does this to store your preferences and track your use of Qriyo App. You understand and agree that Qriyo has every right to share such ID with third parties for its promotions, analysis, etc. 

In case You participate in any other schemes, facilities, services provided by the Qriyo Service, You will be required to provide additional information. Such information will also remain in Qriyo’s database and will be considered as your Personal Information and will be treated as confidential. 

Protection of Information and Storage

Qriyo needs to caution You that the Qriyo Service could be vulnerable to hacking, virus attacks and your personal data may be at risk. Qriyo takes all the necessary and reasonable caution to protect the Qriyo Service and data. 

Cookies

Qriyo may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your Mobile. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable the Qriyo Service to relate your use of the Qriyo Service to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to Qriyo. The Cookies enables Qriyo to remember your choices and some data field contents which you would be required to fill-in. 

Advertisements

On the Qriyo App and/or the Website, Qriyo might post advertisements provided by Advertisers. These Advertisers might set mobile device id on their Apps. Qriyo is not responsible for any of these Advertisers. You on your entire risk and volition are advised to deal with the Advertisers if You intend to. By allowing such advertisements Qriyo do not recommend or market or warranty the Advertisers, quality, commitment, deliverables, genuineness and Advertisers commitment to protect your Personal Information. 

Pre-Approved Sharing of Personal Information

Qriyo endeavours to protect your Personal Information. Qriyo may share your Personal Information with its sponsors, service providers and its business partners. Personal Information could be shared so that you may receive newsletters, offers, information about new products, services, launches, facilities, schemes and other information, if applicable. The information collected from You and other users may be analysed in different manners. Qriyo may also share such analysis with its service providers and its business partners. 

In case Qriyo is required to disclose your Personal Information in order to assist the Government Authority or in adherence to the Court or to protect the interest of the Qriyo Service and/or any particular user(s), Qriyo will disclose it without obtaining prior permission from you. 

Links to Other Websites

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Services. The Services may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by Qriyo (the "Third Party Sites"). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Services do not imply that Qriyo endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies. 

Changes to Privacy Policy

Qriyo have and continue to have the right to modify, change or update Privacy Policy at any time. However, Qriyo will use your Personal Information in a manner consistent with Privacy Policy at the time you shared Personal Information. You are encouraged to check the Qriyo Service often to get updated about Privacy Policy. You acknowledge that by virtue of usage of the Qriyo Service you provide acceptance of the Privacy Policy. All questions to be addressed to **cs@qriyo.com**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: Qriyo Infolabs Pvt. Ltd. 414/ 418 Mansarovar Plaza,   
Jaipur, Rajasthan, India 302020   
cs@qriyo.in 

_This document was last updated on **April 1, 2016**_
